let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "In which year, the term blockchain was first introduced?",
    answer: "2009",
    options:[
      "2003",
      "2008",
      "2010",
      "2009",
    ]
    
},
{
    numb: 2,
    question: "The blockchain was popularised by a person using the name ____.",
    answer : "Satoshi Nakamoto",
    options:[
    "Jeff Bezos ",
    "Elon Musk ",
    "Satoshi Nakamoto",
    "Billy Markus",
    
    ]
},
{
    numb: 3,
    question: "Blocks that are securely linked together using cryptography is known as",
    answer: "Blockchain",
    options:[
    "Blockchain",
    "Metamask",
    "Cryptocurrency",
    "Programming language",
    ]
},
{
    numb: 4,
    question: "Some Features of public blockchain are",
    answer:"All of the above",
    options:[
    "High security",
    "Decentralization",
    "Full transparency",
    "All of the above",
    ]
},
{
    numb: 5,
    question: "The process by which the activities of an organization, particularly those regarding planning and decision making, are distributed or delegated away from a central, authoritative location or group.",
    answer: "Decentralization",
    option:[
    "Centralisation",
    "Decentralization",
    ]
},
{
    numb: 6,
    question: "The type of blockchain in which only entity participating in the transaction have knowledge about the transaction performed whereas others will not be able to access it is ",
    answer: "Private Blockchain",
    option:[
    "Private blockchain",
    "Public blockchain",
    "Hybrid transparency",
    "None of the above",
    ]
},
{
    numb: 7,
    question: "Type of blockchain which amalagamates components of both public and private blockchain",
    answer: "Hybrid Blockchain",
    option:[
    "Hybrid Blockchain",
    "Private blockchain",
    "Public blockchain ",
    "None of the above",
    ]
},
{
    numb: 8,
    question: "What does P2P stand for?",
    answer: "Peer to peer",
    options:[
    "Private to public ",
    "Password to password",
    "Pipe to pipe",
    "Peer to peer",
    ]
},
{
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is a dApp?",
    answer: "A decentralized application",
    options:[
    "A type of Cryptocurrency",
    "A condiment",
    "A type of blockchain",
    "A decentralized application",
    ]

},
{
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is a genesis block?",
    answer: "The first block of a Blockchain",
    options:[
    "The first block of a Blockchain",
    "A famous block that hardcoded a hash of the Book of Genesis onto the blockchain",
    "The first block after each block halving",
    "The 2nd transaction of a Blockchain",]

},
];